Aous Shaheen

Junior Web Developer

Meticulous Web Developer with 2 years of Front-end experience and passion for responsive website design and a firm believer in the mobile-first approach. Driven by a desire to progress professionally and discover new things. Looking for new challenges and opportunities that will expand my skills and assist businesses in building and maintaining superior code bases for reusability.



- Bangalore, India
- github.com/Shaheen121

- +919741670373
- in linkedin.com/in/shaheen2001

EDUCATION

B.Tech Computer ScienceJain University

09/2019 - Present

Banglore, India

PERSONAL PROJECTS

HooBank React Apllication

• React app for a Bank that has a modern UI.

E-commerce shop Website

 E-commerce web application using Next.js and Sanity for the backend.

Modern Dashboard using React

 React app that can be used for displaying all of your website data in one place.

Huddle Landing Page

• Interactive landing page for a company website.

WORK EXPERIENCE

What Can I Do?

Front End Development

06/2021 - Present

What Can I Do?

Back End Development

08/2022 - Present

What Can I Do?

Android Development

04/2022 - Present

SKILLS



CURRENTLY LEARNING

Node JS

Express JS

Laravel

CERTIFICATES

Front-End Development by Meta

Programming with JavaScript by Meta

Advanced Web Development using React by Meta

LANGUAGES

Arabic

English

Full Professional Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Cyber Security and Shell coding

Video Games